Because, you're going to be
joining me on my mission.
You see, I'm planning to beat your boss
and take back this city for the people.
What?
To rid this city of drug dealing
and child abusing mafiosi,
I have no other choice but
to become a mafioso myself.
What are you trying to say?
Surely your mission doesn't
involve joining our Syndicate?
Do you have any idea what you're saying?
What something like that would entail?
Isn't it beautiful?
Yeah,
it's risky, but to take back the city,
I have to join the syndicate that
controls it and work my way to the top.
Bucciarati, trust me,
I'll be a primo mafioso.
I'm open, pass it!
Crazy mille!
Fine then.
I'll report I was unable
to locate Luka's attacker.
Then I'll introduce you to
begin the initiation process.
But you should know,
if it ever gets out that you're
attempting to take down the boss,
I'll be forced to cut ties with you.
A traitor stands alone on
an island of isolation.
Your failure will be
yours and yours alone.
Nothing certain yet, but
your resolve is undeniable.
I respect that kind of nobility, and
I commend your golden aspirations.
You have my support.
Thank you.
We will continue to fight.
We will fight with our enemies!
Fighting gold!
And it's not the boss's actual name.
To be frank, no one knows his true name,
nor does anyone know what he looks like.
Orders are passed down
via a multitude of kapos.
Giorno, the Cape who will decide your
future in the Family is a man named Polpo.
Go on now.
He resides here in this building.
But this is...
It's a prison.
That's right.
Polpo was convicted and promptly
sentenced to 15 years in prison.
He still issues orders
and manages the Family,
but he does it all from
within those walls.
He can leave his confinement whenever the
desire strikes him, but he chooses not to.
He simply has no need.
¿Por qué?
Your answer's inside.
Listen, Giorno.
In a matter of minutes,
he'll conduct your interview.
It's imperative you pass.
It's no different from
an ordinary interview.
His mood will dictate its content.
And remember, he cannot find out.
I understand.
Before I forget, you mentioned
our powers are called stands, yes?
I never asked, how did you acquire yours?
And do others have them?
Once again, the answer's waiting inside.
If you pass.
Before you head in,
I'm going to need your watch and
everything in your pockets on this tray.
After that, you can
move on to the pat-down.
Please stand over there,
hands above your head.
Once we open the gate, proceed forward,
then stop at the end of the hall.
Got it?
Polpo's cell is labeled N-28.
You can't miss it.
Reinforced glass keeps him inside,
but you can still converse.
Keep in mind, exchanging objects either
from him or yourself is strictly forbidden,
so don't try anything.
You only have 15 minutes
to complete your visit.
Once you enter, I'll
close the gate behind you.
If he gets hostile, just
yell and we'll assist you.
I'm talking to him while
he's locked up in his cell?
We're not going to get a special room?
Not a chance.
Don't you realize who he is?
It's injured, isn't it?
Your left arm.
What?
I thought that was a bed.
I spy a faint yet distinct
red marking on the fingers of
your right hand that signifies
you were gripping something.
I'd say they're the markings
left behind by a bag.
And based on that fact, you've been carrying
the bag exclusively in your right hand.
Now why would that be?
Well, first of all, you're correct.
I carried my bag with my right hand.
Also, I did injure my left arm earlier.
I envy your youthful
body and reckless spirit.
By the by, do you drink wine?
This Chianti Classico is molto Bone.
And when paired with a few crackers,
scamorza and the right amount
of caviar, It's perfection.
I'm not allowed to give you anything.
And I can't accept
anything from you either.
That's just a silly formality.
What people say when watched and what
they do when no one else is around
are two entirely different things.
Therein lies the beauty and ugliness
of this fickle thing we call humanity.
I suppose the only real tragedy to
being holed up in this cell is...
Well, Polpo,
he's living like a king, but that's
not the reason he stays put in there.
It wouldn't matter if he left or stayed.
And let's be honest, with that
carcass, he's probably safer in there.
The thing I want to
know is how the hell the
guards even managed to
fit in through the door.
Bucciarati's already
told me all about you.
So you desire to be a part
of our Family, do you?
Uh, it was Giorno Giovanna, wasn't it?
Well then, if you're ready to begin,
let's say we commence with the interview.
What was that?
Am I hallucinating?
For a second, it looked like he
was munching away on his fingers.
Or maybe this cazzone
polpo is simply another
one of those stand users like Bucciarati.
Either way, I have to do whatever it takes
to keep him from finding out about me.
When you're separating
the wheat from the chaff,
what do you think is the most
important factor for one to consider?
Think carefully, Giovanna.
What a person can do, correct?
Oh, then what can you do, ragazzo?
While that guard was patting
me down, I took some souvenirs.
I thought they might come
in handy during our test.
Of course, I'll return them on my way out.
Is that all you brought to impress me?
Well, besides that, I have this
other little trick I can do.
I can fold my ear into my ear canal.
Ah, molto interessante.
But you see, there's something very
important we haven't discussed yet.
And that is the delicate subject
of trust, Giorno Giovanna.
That's the most important quality
in selecting an associate.
They must be trustworthy.
When compared to that
essential characteristic,
intelligence and talent are
no more significant than
this piece of slobbery cracker
stuck between my teeth.
My test will tell me exactly
how trustworthy you are.
The discerning flame of
this lighter reveals all.
Now take it in hand and go.
You are not to let the flame expire.
Aspetta, I warn you,
exercise extreme caution.
The 17th century theologian
Fuller once said,
He's my friend that speaks
well of me behind my back.
You'd do well to remember those words.
If you want to become part of our Family,
you'll need to demonstrate your
trustworthiness even when no one's looking.
24 hours.
That's how long you'll
possess the lighter.
You must never let the flame go out.
If you pass this test,
you'll be welcome to join us.
Straightforward, yes?
And don't worry, there's
plenty of flu in here.
All that's required to pass is for
you to sit in your room until 3 p .m.
tomorrow looking after that flame.
As long as you're truly a man
of prudence and perseverance,
then nothing should happen to that light.
Do this simple task and you will
have proven your trustworthiness.
But don't get too complacent.
If you happen to be the kind of person
who would take what I have to say lightly,
let's say you nod off, or you
sneeze, or maybe you stumble,
or perhaps a gust of wind
extinguishes that precious flame.
I'll know beyond a shadow
of a doubt that you,
my friend, cannot be trusted
as a member of our Family.
Now take the lighter and
be on your way, Cucholo.
Behold the key to our Family.
You have 24 hours.
I look forward to our
second meeting tomorrow.
3 p .m.
Don't be late.
24 hours.
All visitors must proceed through
the gate for a final pat-down.
once we give you permission
to exit the premises
you may proceed to the
next room to retrieve
your belongings wait a second didn't Polpo
say anything to you time
for your search you've
been warned accepting
anything from a convict
is punishable by law
Merida I was banking on the
fact that he would have
bribed these cops to let
me walk out of here with
the lighter scot-free
Atencione!
Hands above your head
and step forward now!
I get it.
Polpo's test has already started.
Which means there's no turning back.
I have to pass.
I have to become a part of the
Passione Family at any cost.
Step forward, nice and slow.
I concealed her ID in the palm of my hand.
I can hide this flame too.
Here we go.
You're good to go.
Doesn't seem to be anything out of order.
You're free to leave the premises.
But first, I ask that
you show me your palms.
I'll say it once more.
You're prohibited from accepting
any objects from convicts.
Now open your hands immediately.
That's an order!
A flower?
Well, what do you know?
This thing is an actual flower.
Fine.
If this is the worst you've
got, you can have it back.
Our visitor is free to go.
I transformed the lighter into a flower
and hid the flame within the petals.
Still, that was too close for comfort.
Now that I think about it, could this
flame actually be part of Polpo's stand?
This wind is a major problem.
Yo, Giorno! Perfect timing!
Hey, could you be a pal and
press the shutter button?
Nope, not a chance.
Excuse me, youngster, but would you
mind lending me a hand with all this?
Not now.
Finally made it back to the dorm.
That was a close one.
Ow.
This should keep it upright.
And even if there's a little draft, it
shouldn't be enough to blow out the light.
Now, as Polpo said,
all I have to do is
remain diligent and watch
this flame with my life for 23 more hours.
Oh, that's right. The window.
I have to make sure it's good and locked.
You never really know when a gust
of wind might suddenly strike.
The hell?
Who would just go and open my door?
Wait, that's...
Hmm, I guess he hasn't come home yet.
It's now or never.
Isn't that the Japanese tourist?
Yeah, it's Koichi Hirose.
How the hell did the guy
find out where I live?
Hmm.
He must have already done something
with my suitcase and everything inside.
Although, he may have left my
passport around here somewhere.
Selling off a personal ID?
That process has got to
be a lot more involved.
I can't believe I'm
sneaking around his room.
I feel like a common thief.
Oh, what am I saying?
He's the thief!
All I'm doing is looking
for what's rightfully mine.
That's right!
His passport! Katsu!
It's in the box on my desk.
I was gonna give it back to him.
It's only a matter of time
before Koichi finds that flame.
There's no question he'll
put it out once he does.
He'll just think it's a fire hazard.
Damn it. Think.
I've got to somehow get that
lighter back before it's too late.
Golden wind!
Awesome.
Golden Wind managed to turn
that lamp cord into a snake.
I had a feeling you'd like that bread.
Nice job digging in.
Now to reel it in.
What the? Shit!
Oh, come on!
He still found the lighter?
Everything's going to hell!
I just need to make sure
he doesn't blow it out!
Huh?
You're kidding me!
That's the Imperial
Seal of Japan! Found it!
I got my passport back!
Ahh!
But I didn't mean to set it on fire!
What a relief.
What the?
That's weird. Where'd it go?
I know I saw a lit lighter here.
Another close call.
That tourist guy almost put
out the flame accidentally.
but nobody's gonna extinguish my dream and
the first step to realizing my goal is.
protecting this flimsy flame with my life.
just missed you.
there you're sorry.
about that was cleaning the
stairs and got carried away.
yeah.
glad you were able to dodge that.
i almost gave you an unwanted shower.
i suppose we both done our
fair share of good deeds today.
wouldn't you say so?
sunny living each day as the good
lord intended is very important.
are you shitting me?
i don't believe it.
the flame.
maybe if i go back and grovel Polpo
will let me start the test over.
no i can't.
if he were that forgiving he wouldn't be
putting me through this
test in the first place.
something wrong.
my what? What do we have here?
Is your lighter not working for you?
That's some bad luck there.
Wait, I didn't break it, did I?
Sorry, but this doesn't concern you.
I'm just trying to figure out
what my next move should be.
From the looks of it, it might
still be in working order.
The lighter itself looks fine.
And if I'm not mistaken, I think I hear
the sucker releasing its fuel. Hang on.
What did you just say?
Hmm? Yes, sir.
There's something coming out of here.
This must be how you switch
it on like this. You see?
No, that's impossible Why would
you be able to turn it back on?
The thing is either on or it's
not That's the point of the test
if I could reignite it whenever I
wanted the test would be futile.
Granted that was more of blowtorch than a
lighter but I think I
got it working again.
So score one for persistence
see? See? Gotta say,
it's kind of strange
you're carrying a lighter
when you don't seem to
be much of a smoker,
but to each his own.
No.
Why'd it reignite?
Something has to be wrong!
What the hell did I just see?
That couldn't be a stand, could it?
You're the one who reignited the flame.
I offer two paths, but you must pick
the one that will lead to salvation.
Shit, I was right.
Time to choose.
Do you live on and
become one of the chosen,
or do you proceed along the path of death?
It's a stand.
And not just any stand, either.
It's got to be Polpo's.
You're the one who reignited the flame.
You shall receive my arrow.
That's too far, Bastardo!
You've messed with the wrong guy.
No!
This is not the one!
This soul does not belong to the chosen!
What's that supposed to mean?
Hey, old man! Are you?
There's not a single wound on him!
But he's dead.
The arrow didn't pierce him
physically, it pierced his soul.
So he rips a person's
soul from their body and
ends their life with a
pierce from the arrow?
Is that how he does it?
He said something about the soul
of the Chosen receiving the arrow.
Is that what they call
someone who joins the Family?
You two have reignited the flame!
Salvation awaits!
Prepare, as before you light two paths!
Every time I close my eyes.
Wake up feeling so horny!
I can't get you out of my mind.
Since you'll be all I see?
I would give anything.
Just to make you understand me!
I don't give a damn about nothing else.
Freaking you is all I need!
Tonight I need your mind.
I need your mind.
Tonight you got my time.
I'll give it to you.
Tonight you won't decide.
Tonight you got my mind.
If you've got my mind, all
I want to do is free you.
What must I say?
Oh, tell me.
What must I do?
To show how much I'm going to free you.
What must I say?
What must I do?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
To show how much I'm going to free you.
I'm freaking out.
Thank you.